foxconn.com 2019-03-09

# Privacy Statement

Privacy

* * *

###  Privacy Statement

To ensure the security of your personal information, Foxconn hereby declares as below its privacy policy. This statement will apply to Foxconn websites worldwide

###  PURPOSE FOR ACQUIRING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Generally, you can visit Foxconn’s websites without giving us your name or other personal information. But there are times when Foxconn may need information from you to complete a transaction or to provide a better service, for instance, to process an order, to correspond or in connection with a job application. 

###  USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern of Foxconn. The ultimate purpose in using your information is to support and enhance our relationship with you, for instance, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news with you. Foxconn will in no event sell your personal information. Foxconn only share your personal data outside the companies of Foxconn Technology Group with your consent, as required by law, or with partners that help Foxconn fulfill its obligations to you and who share the commitment hereof to protecting your privacy. Foxconn will safeguard and protect against unauthorized access, use and disclosure of your information by using appropriate measures and processes to maintain security.

###  THIRD-PARTY SITES

Please be aware that other websites that may be accessed through this website may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party websites linked to this website are not covered by this privacy statement. Foxconn is not responsible for the privacy practices of the websites that it does not operate. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Foxconn cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Foxconn, and you do so at your own risk.

###  UPDATE OF INFORMATION

Foxconn wants to help you keep your personal information accurate. If there is any change to your information, please notify us for updating.

###  CONTACT US

If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy policy, please write to us at the following address: 

  * Hon Hai Precision Industry Co., Ltd.
  * No.2, Zihyou St., Tucheng Dist.,
  * New Taipei City 236,
  * Taiwan
  * E-mail:[WebAdmin@foxconn.com](mailto:WebAdmin@foxconn.com)
